THE FIRST QUEST OF THE DESCEND CLUB
WATCH THE SUNRISE FROM TAEBAEKSAN
SUNRISE EXPECTED AT 7:37 A.M.
CURRENT LOCATION
YUILSA SHELTER
52 MINUTES LEFT UNTIL THE SUN RISES
One remaining 30-minute section
is as difficult as the beginning was.
Think of it as 30 difficult minutes
and 30 easy minutes.
-Okay.
-All right.
Let's go quickly.
Let's go while we're still fine.
It's rising.
It's coming up.
LEAVING THE YUILSA SHELTER
THEY'RE TAKING LONGER THAN EXPECTED
ON THE TRAIL
THE STEEP SECTION STARTS IMMEDIATELY
Well, this is nothing
compared to Seoraksan.
My thoughts exactly.
THE YOUNGER MEMBERS WITH GOOD STAMINA
CAR, THE GARDEN TAKES LEAD
THE FIRST STAIRCASE OF THIS TRAIL APPEARS
CAR, THE FAST WALKER SPEEDS UP
THEY HURRIEDLY MOVE PAST THE STAIRS
NEXT IS THE STONE STAIRCASE SECTION
CAR, THE GARDEN
FROM DOWOON'S CAM
SIGHS
I'm beat.
It's okay. Take it slow.
What?
You can walk. Take it slow. It's fine.
I'm walking very slowly.
Really? That's good.
Oh, no. It's getting brighter.
It's okay. That's the light of dawn.
We got up at 2:00 a.m. for this.
-We have to see it.
-Yeah, we must.
I think it'd feel so unfair if we miss it.
Exactly. I'll get angry.
We have to see it.
I seriously thought, "If we fail,
it'll be so disappointing."
I mean, we even sacrificed sleep for this.
"We have to pull this off."
That's what I was thinking.
SIGHS
I must've strained it somehow.
Halfway through, this part here
started to hurt.
It's annoying when your leg hurts.
And you have a mountain to climb.
It's like eating with an injured finger.
It's annoying.
That's how it felt.
FATIGUED FROM HIKING IN TWO DAYS
This is bullshit.
Absolute bullshit.
SUDDEN AND UNEXPECTED LEG PAIN
I give up.
GOING THROUGH
A DIFFICULT FIGHT WITH HIMSELF
CAR, THE GARDEN
FROM DOWOON'S CAM
Should we stop here
for just a bit of water?
All right.
-Sorry?
-Let's drink some water.
Goodness.
It sure is steep.
A SHORT BREAK THANKS TO DOWOON
Here you go.
HELPER DOWOON PROVIDES A SPORTS DRINK
-You can drink first.
-Thanks.
I have water too.
COLLECTS TRASH
I feel hot already.
SATISFIED SIGH
LOOKING PROUDLY
THEY CATCH A BREATHER
THANKS TO HELPER DOWOON
I think we're almost there.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
Let's go.
45 MINUTES BEFORE SUNRISE
GETTING HIGHER AND HIGHER
The sky is so pretty.
Look at that gradient of color.
Exactly.
THE NATURAL GRADIENT OF COLOR
MADE BY THE LIGHT OF DAWN
It sure is beautiful.
Tarzzan should write
some rap lyrics inspired by that.
It really is beautiful.
The moon is up in the sky too.
Look at the moon. Gosh.
The sun on one side
and the moon on the other.
Exactly.
The moon and the sky look so beautiful.
They're exactly the colors I like.
The moon is so beautiful.
The moon was floating above the branches,
and it was just so…
Violet?
It reminded me of the movie
The Twilight Saga: Eclipse.
I wanted to take out my phone
to take a photo,
but my hands were frozen.
I just captured it with my eyes
and saved it to my brain.
I thought,
"The GoPro must've captured it."
Yeah, it was like that.
It says 1.4 km.
40 MINUTES BEFORE SUNRISE
1.4 KM TO CHEONJEDAN ALTAR
SIGHS
THE PAIN REAPPEARS
Goodness.
-You can do this.
-Let's go.
Take it slow. It's okay.
-Okay.
-Take a break.
We just need to run
100-m sprints 14 times, and it's over.
HE BEGINS WALKING AGAIN
STAIRS YET AGAIN
AN AWKWARD SMILE
-Should we rest?
-No, I can't.
Let me rest for just 30 seconds.
Okay. Let's wait.
HIS BODY ISN'T LISTENING TO HIM
More stairs had to show up.
Goodness.
How refreshing.
Isn't this nice?
I wanted to see your face.
I missed you.
TA-DA
-You can go now.
-Let's go.
We can do it.
His leg pain seemed to be
a lot worse than I thought.
He kept checking on it.
But he didn't panic at the pain.
I would've panicked.
Even in that condition,
he quietly did what he had to do.
It's only meaningful
if we all go together.
So we went at the same pace.
DESCEND CLUB MEMBERS
HIKE AT THE SAME PACE
We're almost there. Hang in there.
We're almost there.
PAUSES
THE SNOW IS STILL PILED UP HERE
The trail…
Is this really a trail?
We're literally making a path.
FROM EPISODE 3
YOU NEED TO RUSSELL THIS SECTION
This is so beautiful.
What's with this place?
The stretched-out branches look so pretty.
I know, right?
It's something you'd see
in Beauty and the Beast.
LIKE A SNOW TUNNEL FROM A FAIRY TALE
THE SIGHT MAKES THEM FORGET
THE EXHAUSTION OF CLIMBING UPHILL
I'm sorry to do this while you're tired,
but I'll explain one thing.
Here.
You really are persistent too.
WE KNOW WE'RE PERSISTENT
BUT WE WANT TO SHOW YOU THIS SCENERY
This is called "rime."
Snow is piled up on the branches.
RIME
WATER VAPOR FREEZES
ON BRANCHES IN SUB-ZERO TEMPERATURES
AND LOOKS LIKE WHITE BLOSSOMS
FLOWERS MADE OF SNOW
BLOOM ON WINTER TREES
A BEAUTIFUL SCENE OF WHITE
FOUND IN THE SNOWY MOUNTAINS
This is a yew tree.
They're said to last 1,000 years living
and 1,000 years dead.
YEW TREE
IT LIVES IN ALTITUDES
ABOVE 700 M ABOVE SEA LEVEL
THEY CAN BE VERY LONG-LIVED
YEW TREES GROW WILD ON TAEBAEKSAN
These are yew trees.
This is Korea's biggest yew tree colony.
So as you pass by, you can see
a lot of unusual-looking trees.
Is this show funded by the government?
This is like those absurd ads
in The Truman Show.
He says stuff like this out of nowhere.
Did you watch The Truman Show?
In the movie, the wife of the protagonist
suddenly and awkwardly
starts to advertise things.
What he does feels just like that.
It's not the right time for it,
but he goes, "So this is…"
As if he's obligated to say it.
I just had to explain this one.
Nothing else.
Okay, the yew tree colony.
-Yew tree colony.
-Let's go.
Ew tree colony?
Yew tree colony?
Ye…
-It was "ye" something.
-"Ye."
Ye…
Yet…
Yet tree.
Yen tree.
Yep tree.
Was it the yew tree?
Right.
I remember because I planted that tree
in Hongneung Forest.
I planted a yew tree once
for a YouTube video.
"The tree I planted with My Day."
So there's a DAY6 tree.
"Long after we're gone,
this tree will still be here."
That's what I thought when I planted it.
26 MINUTES BEFORE SUNRISE
Let's check the time.
-What time is it?
-It's 7:11 a.m.
-Eleven?
-Yes.
Okay. In this case, if we're late
about five minutes, it's not our fault.
THEY HAVE ENOUGH TIME TO REACH THE SUMMIT
The sun's going to rise soon.
I can tell from how the sky looks.
THE SKY BECOMES BRIGHTER
This is…
Sir, I…
-Producer.
-Yes?
-I need…
-A break?
It's really bad.
-Your legs?
-Here.
-Really?
-It feels like they're tearing.
I wanted to say it earlier,
but I thought we were close.
When Jung-won said it was an emergency,
I suddenly got scared too.
Go on ahead first.
No, I don't think resting is a good idea.
I'll move to the back. Go ahead.
To the back?
Resting will only make us feel cold.
Let's go.
-Okay.
-I'll go to the back.
Then…
You feel your thighs will cramp?
They already are.
The back of his leg is cramping.
When he said, "Let's just go,"
I thought he was really…
He did this,
and he kept walking.
"He must want to clear this quest too."
I felt that from him.
You go ahead. Let's go.
It's too cold to stay here.
-We're almost there.
-Okay.
DOWOON AND TARZZAN GO FIRST
CAR, THE GARDEN AND CHAE-MIN FOLLOW SUIT
DOWOON, TARZZAN
CAR, THE GARDEN, CHAE-MIN
TAKING EACH STEP WITH DIFFICULTY
THE INSTRUCTOR WANTS TO APPLY FIRST AID
Let's check Jung-won's leg
before we continue.
It's okay.
-Let's just go.
-Are you sure?
Yes. Please, let's just go.
-You can do it.
-Thanks.
DOWOON AND TARZZAN SET OFF FIRST AGAIN
CURRENT LOCATION
SUMMIT
CAR, THE GARDEN IS DEEP IN THOUGHT
THEY START HIKING AGAIN
Darn it.
Damn it.
My gosh.
Seriously…
-I…
-Yes?
I really can't do this show. Seriously.
-Car-the.
-Goodness.
Car-the.
I really can't do this show.
MAKES A NEGATIVE COMMENT
HE'S HELD BACK ALL DAY
Jung-won?
Jung-won.
-You know, right?
-Yes.
NEGATIVE GARDEN
-Can you do this show?
-Of course.
POSITIVE GARDEN
-It's beautiful.
-You're full of lies.
Exactly. The mountain is beautiful.
It's beautiful.
Look behind you. It's so beautiful.
When you struggle physically,
you definitely become weak.
You become vulnerable.
You start making a lot of excuses.
When you're so tired,
you get mentally weak too.
So I thought,
"Those who hang on to their senses
even when they're exhausted
are truly amazing."
-Let's wait for them.
-Yeah.
I felt anxious, but I thought I shouldn't.
I thought Jung-won would feel pressured.
I'm sure he was thinking the same thing.
"We can't slow down because of me."
He must've thought that.
I just…
didn't want to pressure him.
"What? That quest?"
"Come on. As if the reward for it
will be that great."
I wanted to express
those feelings to him.
We're almost there.
We're here.
The uphill part is over.
Here…
Let's just go.
-It's cold.
-Okay.
We have five minutes to go.
We'll arrive in five minutes.
Nice.
10 MINUTES BEFORE SUNRISE
We're almost there.
Would you like to take a break?
Are you all right?
6 MINUTES BEFORE SUNRISE
What time is it?
It's 7:31 a.m.
The sun is slowly rising.
It should fully rise
when we get to Janggunbong Peak.
THE SUN PEEKS OUT SLIGHTLY
We're really here.
JANGGUNBONG IS JUST OVER THE HILL
THEY MARCH TO THE HILL
WITH ALL THEIR REMAINING STRENGTH
Isn't this a successful completion?
ARRIVED AT JANGGUNBONG
-What's the time?
-It's 7:33 a.m.
That means…
Seeing the sunrise on Taebaeksan.
You've cleared the quest.
THE FIRST QUEST IS COMPLETE
Good job, Jung-won.
Good job.
-Good job.
-Well done.
Good job, everyone.
When I saw the sunrise?
We did have to rush our hike,
as if someone was chasing us.
But still,
we saw the sun on the horizon.
The sun rose just in time too.
So, yeah…
It was really nice.
JANGGUNBONG
As soon as we got up there,
it was the summit,
and nothing else was higher than that.
The open view was really beautiful.
Actually, I wanted
to stay up there longer,
but there was no suitable place to stay.
The wind was blowing so hard.
CURRENT WIND SPEED
"STRONG"
My gloves!
GLOVES FLY AWAY IN THE WIND
My hands are frozen. I can't untie this.
WEARING PADDED JACKETS
TO SHIELD AGAINST THE STRONG WIND
It definitely was pretty windy.
It was so cold up there.
I was stunned.
It was way too cold today.
RUSTLING
Jung-won, at least eat this.
It's okay.
You can't eat at all?
No.
What would you like?
-Thank you, Dowoon.
-What do you want to eat?
I'll go with the cocoa ball bar.
HELPER DOWOON WORKS HARD AT THE SUMMIT TOO
Why don't you have one?
Is it harder to eat?
I'll keep one, then.
Thanks.
Okay.
Let's take a photo, everyone.
LAST-MINUTE SUGAR BOOST
BEFORE TAKING PHOTOS
DESCEND CLUB'S FIRST PHOTO
WITH A SUMMIT MARKER
YUM
TAKING A GROUP PHOTO IN THE BITING WIND
GETTING CHOKED UP
Here we go. One, two, three.
JANUARY 14, 2026
SUNRISE AT JANGGUNBONG, TAEBAEKSAN
Shall we strike a pose?
Like a peace sign or a fist pump?
-Let's go!
One, two, three.
I wanted to go down quickly.
It was so cold. I just…
Taking photos was so hard.
You need to force yourself
to look excited.
The face we wanted to make
was that.
-One more time.
-With a good view of the sun too.
FAKE EXCITEMENT
Put your hands up.
Last photo. One, two, three.
When we were taking the photos,
I couldn't smile
because it was so cold.
My cheeks had frozen.
But…
Dowoon gave out his energy bars,
so I felt a bit better after eating it.
This is good.
I told you. You need to eat.
There's a reason we refuel with sugar.
Thank you.
Thanks for the energy bar.
No problem.
-Thank you.
-Sure.
CHOMPING
This tastes good.
Eating this revived me.
Do you want a bite?
I'm good.
But then again, food always comes first.
CHOMPING AGAIN
I remember the chocolate bar tasted good.
Who gave it to you?
Dowoon.
He is today's MVP.
TARZZAN'S TAEBAEKSAN MVP
I felt good after giving those out.
I felt good.
When you hike, you crave sugar.
You really crave sugar.
When you take a bite of an energy bar,
you think,
"Did these always taste this good?"
MEANWHILE, THE ONE WHO REFUSED TO EAT
Jung-won declined once.
"It's okay." He refused like this.
I said, "You should still try it."
I gave him one, and he really enjoyed it.
That guy always refuses
to listen at first.
CHECKING ON THAT GUY'S CONDITION
Behind my knee.
-Behind your knee?
-Here.
Since we'll be going down,
it should be fine.
I'll give it a try.
YUM
Let's go.
THEY START TO DESCEND
TAKING THE DANGGOL PLAZA TRAIL DOWNHILL
Now, it's "good morning."
Yeah.
THE DESCENT BEGINS
Once we're down,
some barbecue would be amazing.
Gosh, Tarzzan.
Yes?
Going downhill is so easy.
Right?
My ankles…
What a magnificent view.
It sure is beautiful, though.
It's spectacular.
I'd never get to see
something like this again.
The view on my right.
WHERE THE MORNING SUN SHINES
The scenery around me felt quite flat.
That made it even more beautiful.
I think I got to see
what a real snow mountain looks like.
My hands are so cold.
THEY ARRIVE AT THE CHEONJEDAN
TAEBAEKSAN
What does that say?
I think that indicates the summit.
So a lot of people take photos here.
CHEONJEDAN, JANGGUNBONG
ANOTHER POPULAR SPOT
FOR SEEING THE SUNRISE
TAEBAEKSAN
THE PLACE WHERE TAEBAEKSAN'S
STONE ALTAR IS LOCATED
I'm on Taebaeksan, everyone.
Taebaeksan.
FIRST TIME PROVING HE'S AT THE SUMMIT
YOU CAN CHECK ON CCTV AS WELL
The mountains you see beyond mountains
are called sangeurime.
"San?"
Sangeurime. It's a pure Korean word.
-"Geurimhae"?
-They look like shadows.
SANGEURIME OR MOUNTAIN SILHOUETTE
THE FAINT VIEW OF DISTANT MOUNTAINS
LINED UP IN LAYERS LIKE SHADOWS
This is easy.
THE DESCENT STARTS AGAIN
Doesn't it feel like
an amusement park in the winter?
-A winter amusement park?
-Yeah.
-Why?
-If you go to Everland in the winter…
Yeah?
You can ride sleds and so on.
But what good does that do?
We can't get on any sleds.
I should bring a pack next time.
What am I saying? I mean a sack.
Yeah, I think we could ride it
as long as it's not Seoraksan.
I know, right?
I saw your Instagram yesterday.
You were number one
on the Apple Music chart.
Yes, number one on Apple Music.
Congratulations.
And 26th on Melon.
It's my first time ranking so high.
Number 26 on Melon?
Yes.
ON THE DAY OF FILMING
CAR, THE GARDEN'S SONG "MY WHOLE WORLD"
HAD A RESURGENCE
AND TOPPED A MUSIC CHART
TODAY'S TOP 100 IN KOREA
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
In the end, the song
became a belated success.
All sorts of things can happen in life.
My fellow musicians call me
"the icon of toughing it out."
Only now, I am…
I'm a bit embarrassed to say
it's thanks to my music.
I was able to catch people's attention
with variety show-like content.
I mean, any attention
is still good attention.
But at the end of the day, I'm a musician.
It's nice for my songs to get noticed.
So I was working hard.
-I got excited yesterday.
-Right.
I should've slept at midnight.
You posted on Instagram.
People from my agency
kept hyping me up.
I couldn't sleep until 1:00 a.m.
LAST NIGHT
Jung-won, you're number one
on Apple Music in Korea.
I'm with Korea's
number one singer right now.
To be honest, I feel very happy today.
This is my first time experiencing this.
HUMMING
But the thing is
I always share song copyrights equally
with my bandmates who I love
and always work with.
I never consider who worked more on what.
Because I never thought
I'd ever chart that high.
But as I was hiking, I thought,
"Damn it."
"Should I change the split?"
"I think I worked more on this song."
BLACK-HEARTED
I'm such a poor excuse for a human being.
I'm so low-quality as a person.
You get what I mean?
I'm so lame.
"Jung-won, since you're exhausted,
you're being so lame."
So lame.
It's like whenever Gollum
is near the One Ring.
You start acting like that.
HAS A LOT ON HIS MIND
At least the way down
is pretty smooth, right?
Yeah.
I like how there are no rocks.
Yeah, and I can even look around.
Exactly. I can look around today.
Yeah.
THE SNOWSCAPE SHINES BRIGHTER
IN THE MORNING SUN
If Seoraksan had very exciting vibes,
then this place had relaxed
and comforting vibes.
Your body is cold,
but your heart feels warm
while on the mountain.
That's the energy it gives off.
Rather than the sunrise itself,
the snowy mountain scenery
was more beautiful.
THEY ENJOY THE SNOWSCAPE
AS THEY DESCEND
I like how the ground feels here.
BANJAE PASS
How far have we come?
About one-third?
You're halfway there.
THEY TAKE A SHORT BREAK
Want some candy?
No, I'm good.
Are your legs okay?
No, they hurt.
DEPRESSED
-Do you want some caramel?
-Should I have one?
Yeah, if you're hungry.
YOON DORAEMON HAS
AN INFINITE SUPPLY OF TRAIL FOOD
Go on ahead.
We're opening caramels.
We'll be right there.
Go ahead.
The caramels have frozen.
Right.
Every time we descend like this,
I realize that we climbed up a long way.
I'm not going to think anymore.
You shouldn't think.
As you walk, just empty your head
and trust it'll end sooner or later.
CHAE-MIN STOPS WALKING
Dowoon.
Do you see that round tomb?
The one hidden by the tree?
Right in front here.
-This one.
-It's a tomb?
-You see that?
-Yeah.
They say it's a stone tomb for those
who were bitten and killed by a tiger.
Really?
They're buried here.
So tigers appear here.
I guess so.
HOSIKCHONG TOMBS
A GRAVE FOR PEOPLE BITTEN
AND KILLED BY TIGERS
PRECIOUS FOLK MATERIAL SHOWING A GLIMPSE
OF LIVES AND BELIEFS OF PEOPLE OF THE PAST
It's so sad they were
bitten to death by tigers.
Did you see Hosikchong?
Yes.
Are there tigers in Taebaeksan?
I guess tigers used to live here.
Not now though, right?
There aren't any here now.
What should you do
if you run into one here?
When you see a tiger,
should you pretend not to see it?
Just ignore the wild animals.
-Sorry?
-Ignore them.
Ignore them?
So if a wild boar is in front of me,
I should…
THEY LEARNED THIS DURING THEIR LESSON
I should do this?
THE DOCENT IS ON STANDBY
At this location, there's something called
"The Amazing Green Carpet Moss."
It's covered in snow,
so it's hard to see now.
But there's a bunch of moss here
that goes all the way up.
-So…
-Yes?
I'm sorry,
but we can't see the moss at all
since it's covered in snow.
So why are you explaining it?
Oh, there it is.
Yes.
Is it this?
So it's not just any moss?
Yes, it's called "green carpet moss."
It spreads all the way up there.
FACT
IT'S JUST MOSS
Then, is it different from normal moss?
I need to check.
Isn't this like
educational material you turn on
for elementary school students?
The EBS channel.
If you think about it,
kids would like you lot.
You're right.
Are you sending this video file to EBS?
It turns out this show
is for EBS, not Netflix.
I think you'd be capable of such a lie.
He keeps breaking the flow.
LAUGHING
The flow…
We'd still be climbing up
Seoraksan at this time.
Exactly.
How did we do it?
It's scary to think about.
I'm amazed that we did it.
Seriously, how did we hike there?
But if the first mountain was Taebaeksan,
and the second one was Seoraksan,
it would've felt even harder.
I agree.
They planned the order well.
Are they going to take us
to Baekdusan next?
I really want to go to a hot spring.
AS THEY TALK ABOUT THIS AND THAT
Seriously, the next time we go somewhere…
-We should go.
-We have to go if they have one.
We must be almost all the way down.
-We're almost done.
-We're here.
I see houses.
I see a greenhouse.
You worked so hard, Jung-won.
-Really.
-No, you guys worked hard.
Jung-won, we'll see you
on the next filming day, right?
COUGHING
LAUGHING
Is today our last day together?
Let's do a heartfelt goodbye just in case.
Later, when we say goodbye…
-Let's do a proper one.
-Yes, just in case.
-We'll hug and everything.
-Yeah.
We could see each other somewhere else.
We could meet happily.
I feel like I have
some stamina left today.
Don't say that.
Just say you spent
the right amount. Sorry?
Don't say that.
Just say you spent
the right amount. Sorry?
-You have energy left?
-No, we're good.
It's enough energy to eat
and lift the spoon.
Enough to chat while eating--
Want to go for another hike?
There's Hambaeksan next to this one.
No.
Want to go see the sun glow at dusk?
Want to see the sunset?
No.
I want to see the sunset in Seoul.
ARRIVAL AT DANGGOL PLAZA
I'll see it from N Seoul Tower.
I'll take the elevator.
We've arrived at Danggol Plaza.
HIKE FINISHED
-The descent is complete.
-Good work, everyone.
We'll go and eat now.
-Okay.
-This is The Mountaineer's Oath.
Should we read it before we go?
Could you…
AN ENGRAVED STONE STANDING ALONE
THE MOUNTAINEER'S OATH
BY NOSAN LEE EUN-SANG
Could you recite it for us, President Tar?
You should take the oath.
"The Mountaineer's Oath."
-I swear.
I swear.
"Mountaineers explore
the endless universe."
"Until we arrive at the destination,
we will overcome all hardships
through passion and cooperation."
"Until we arrive at the destination,
we will overcome all hardships
through passion and cooperation."
"We will never despair nor give up."
Why is it so funny when you read that?
"Mountaineers
must assimilate with nature."
"Without deception or pretense."
"But to the world
of true freedom, peace, and love."
"We will march toward it."
The words were really moving.
THE OATH MOVES MOUNTAINEERS' HEARTS
-Anyway, good job.
-Thank you.
You did great work hiking.
Good job, everyone.
The oath was rather meaningful to me.
I could speak in a loud voice
for the first time.
HOW DID IT FEEL TO HIKE TAEBAEKSAN?
That was exactly how I'd imagined
a mountain view would look,
not like Seoraksan's.
That's my personal preference
if I have to compare the two.
But it was so cold.
I'm serious.
It was really cold when we filmed
the music video for "Famous."
That was one of the coldest days
of my life.
But this set a new record for cold.
Maybe I should gain some weight for this.
WHICH MOUNTAIN WAS EASIER?
TAEBAEKSAN OR SEORAKSAN?
I'd still say Taebaeksan.
Who would choose Seoraksan?
Why on earth do people hike?
I think I'll be reminded of this
on days when I wake up early
and don't go hiking.
We keep…
starting hikes in an unhealthy way.
I still don't know
why on earth people hike.
Honestly, I still don't know yet.
I still don't understand
why people use only their legs to walk up.
You should ride a snowmobile,
walk about 50 m,
take a photo,
put your helmet back on,
and ride back down on the snowmobile.
That would be fun.
Why on earth do you think people hike?
I'll only know if we do more of the show.
We'll be hiking more mountains anyway.
Right? Let's hike some more and see.
We'll hike some more,
and I'll decide if I want
to cut ties with mountains later.
I feel like
you're the person
who is best suited for mountains.
Me?
That was the loudest I've spoken today.
SEORAKSAN TRAINING
WATCHING THE SUNRISE ON TAEBAEKSAN
My leg muscles are all stiff right now.
THEY'RE GOING TO GO TO EAT NOW
See you soon.
Geez.
THEY CAN'T HELP BUT MOAN
AS SOON AS HE SITS
HE OPENS UP TO YAWN WITH NO RESISTANCE
-Good night.
EVERYONE FALLS ASLEEP
PERHAPS DREAMING OF HIKING?
MEANWHILE, THE BUS LEAVES TAEBAEKSAN
IT DRIVES INTO THE CITY
AND ARRIVES AT THE RESTAURANT
We'll get off the bus now.
ALREADY?
I fell asleep as soon as I closed my eyes.
GASPS
THE TERRIBLE AFTEREFFECTS OF HIKING
DESCEND CLUB ARRIVES AT…
This is a famous place
that was on Huh Young-man's Food Travel.
MODERN DINER
A FAMOUS RESTAURANT IN TAEBAEK
THE RESTAURANT'S MAIN DISH
HIGH-QUALITY KOREAN BEEF FROM TAEBAEK
THE KEY IS TO GRILL USING BRIQUETTES
LIKE MINERS BEFORE THE 1990S
THE SMOKY SCENT OF THE GRILL
WITH SWEET AND SALTY BEEF TARTARE
ON THE SIDE
Gosh.
DESCEND CLUB ENTERS
It's one of the best 100 restaurants
in Korea.
-Right.
-We should try it out.
Shall we order
assorted beef and beef tartare?
-Sure.
PRESIDENT TAR MAKES THE ORDER
-Gosh.
-Geez.
I want to go to Seoul.
How will I do my shoot tomorrow?
WORRIED ABOUT TOMORROW DUE TO SORENESS
I should go home and sit
in the massage chair for two hours.
I'll use my leg massagers.
AS THEY MAKE PLANS FOR RECOVERY
THEIR ORDERED FOOD ARRIVES
The meat is good quality here.
Taebaek is famous for its beef.
HE CAN'T TAKE HIS EYES OFF OF IT
-I'll grill the meat.
-Okay.
I'll grill it very lightly.
CHAE-MIN WILL COOK
-Thanks.
-I like it rare.
-I'll start right away.
-Okay.
Have some beef tartare first.
Should I?
BEEF TARTARE AS AN APPETIZER
I've often seen redder ones.
It's salty but it's good.
THEIR FIRST MEAL IN 9 HOURS
This beef tartare is so good.
Eat up.
YUM
I've never seen this kind of color before.
TAKES ANOTHER BITE
This beef tartare is insane.
It's a bit spicy too.
THE OLDER MEMBERS TAKE A BITE TOO
Pass me some tongs. Let's cook together.
ASSISTANT: TARZZAN
THEY START GRILLING NOW
ADDING SMOKY FLAVOR FROM THE BRIQUETTES
The meat here is really good.
The meat is good.
I won't ruin it.
I think we can eat these.
-So go ahead?
-They're rare.
Please eat up.
YUM
-Gosh.
THE COOKS ARE SATISFIED
It's delicious.
DIPPING IT IN SALT
This is so good.
Now, this is it.
HE WAS TOO HASTY
COUGHING
THEY KEEP GRILLING THE MEAT NONSTOP
Chae-min.
-You eat it.
-No, hurry. The sauce is spilling.
YOU FIRST
NO, YOU FIRST
There you go.
EATING CAREFULLY THIS TIME
Gosh.
It sure tastes good.
Everyone's eating a lot.
We have to eat up.
-Having this much beef is rare.
-Right.
DESCEND CLUB RULE
WHEN HIKING IS COMPLETE,
FREE FOOD IS PROVIDED
THEY ATE THEIR FILL
WITH PRODUCTION'S MONEY
I'm starting to feel sleepy.
Me too.
That's normal.
That's right.
I hate the term "normal" now
because it sounds like "summit."
AVERSION TO NORMALCY AND SUMMITS
How long were we at the summit for?
About five minutes?
We couldn't stay there for long.
It was too windy.
We ate the energy bars, took photos,
and came down.
BEFITTING OF THE NAME "DESCEND CLUB"
The energy bar was so delicious.
That's why I told you to eat it.
FRUSTRATED
I'll listen to you guys now.
If you tell me to eat something,
I'll eat it.
MATURED GARDEN
Do you prefer Seoraksan or Taebaeksan?
-Taebaeksan.
Who would want to walk
on a mountain for ten hours?
THE 9 HOURS 32 MINUTES ON SEORAKSAN
It was like taking an exam.
The time taken for this one
was just right.
If it weren't for the time limit,
you could've taken your time to hike,
and it would've been fine.
NODDING
You had to make it before sunrise,
so you didn't stop.
THE YOUNGER MEMBERS NOD
We were hasty at first.
You become impatient.
MOUNTAIN ALLERGY TRIGGERED
If it weren't for that…
Yes, it'd feel like a picnic.
A WORD FROM THE FOREIGN AFFAIRS MINISTER
I can already picture
the press conference for the premiere.
A reporter asks, "Who's the best?"
And I say Chae-min.
PRODUCER NAH PLANS AHEAD BY HIMSELF
I promise you. I'm not lying.
I won't be at the press conference.
I promise you.
SHOCKING DECLARATION
Jung-won,
I kind of missed this side of you.
You were way too positive while hiking.
Right, I should reveal the second quest.
Today's first quest
was seeing the sunrise on Taebaeksan.
All of you saw the sunrise.
Congratulations. You cleared the quest.
FIRST QUEST COMPLETE
FEELING PROUD
Here's the 25 km badge.
It was 25 km?
We walked 25 km today?
Seoraksan was 17 km.
SEORAKSAN
17 KM ROUND TRIP
TAEBAEKSAN
8 KM ROUND TRIP
SEORAKSAN, 17 KM
PLUS TAEBAEKSAN, 8 KM
TOTAL 25 KM WALKED
So we walked a total of 25 km?
-Yes.
-We'll hit 100 km quickly.
Have you prepared the next show?
HE'LL CHANGE THE SHOW
IF THEY GO OVER 100 KM
The second quest will now be revealed.
SIGHING
The second quest
is Baengnokdam Crater Lake
at Hallasan Mountain.
Goodbye!
Baengnokdam Crater Lake.
1,950 M ABOVE SEA LEVEL
HALLASAN IS THE HIGHEST MOUNTAIN IN KOREA
VERY TOUGH FOR BEGINNER HIKERS
I somewhat expected it,
but you're doing exactly that.
I thought this would be our last quest.
DRONE FILMING WAS ALLOWED AFTER DISCUSSION
WITH HALLASAN NATIONAL PARK
HALLASAN
RISING FROM THE CENTER OF JEJU ISLAND
IS A MOUNTAIN WITH AN ELEVATION OF 1,950 M
HIGHER THAN THE CLOUDS
AND CLOSEST TO THE SKY
SHAPED OVER TIME BY NATURE
THE HABITAT OF VARIOUS ORGANISMS
AND THE TOP OF HALLASAN
BAENGNOKDAM
MANY MOUNTAINEERS DREAM
TO SEE THIS LANDSCAPE
BUT DUE TO THE EVER-CHANGING CLOUDS
AND THE FREQUENT FOG THAT COVERS IT
THEY SAY YOU NEED
THREE GENERATIONS OF LUCK
TO CLEARLY SEE BAENGNOKDAM
DRONE FILMING WAS ALLOWED AFTER DISCUSSION
WITH HALLASAN NATIONAL PARK
2ND QUEST
BAENGNOKDAM, HALLASAN
So, with Hallasan…
Let him talk first.
Let him talk.
We need to leave today anyway.
HE WANTS TO LEAVE NOW
So let him talk first.
Hallasan?
How bad is Hallasan?
When compared to Seoraksan?
I heard it's better than Seoraksan.
It's slightly easier.
THE SLOPE IS LOWER AND THE PATH IS LONGER
We'll suffer when we descend.
HE WORRIES ABOUT DESCENDING FIRST
WORRIED ABOUT WIND
Jeju Island will be very windy.
AND ALTITUDE SICKNESS
Elevation is 1,950 m.
FULL OF CONCERNS
We heard him out.
-Let's go home.
-Let's think about it.
It'll be for three days and two nights.
We hike one day… I mean rest one day.
HE'S CURIOUS ABOUT THE SCHEDULE
Then, hike one day…
Chae-min.
SHUSH
LET'S STOP HERE TODAY
Let's go.
Okay.
AFTER THE FIRST SHOOT ENDS
You look like brothers.
GO-HOME GARDEN IS HAPPY NOW
-Good job.
-Take care.
Please go to the hospital.
See you.
-Bye.
-Good job today.
-See you next week.
-Thank you.
-Take care.
-Bye.
-Have a safe flight.
-Thank you.
DOWOON LEAVES TOO
I knew I'd be the last one to go.
CHAE-MIN IS ALONE
I knew I'd be the last one.
Our camera operator said
you kept smiling.
He was smiling.
It was funny how the older members
were struggling.
JOKING
They're cute.
Rather than funny, they're cute.
THE NEXT DAY
DOWOON
HOW ARE YOUR LEGS?
CAR, THE GARDEN
A BIT BETTER
DOWOON
HANG IN THERE
CHAE-MIN
I NEED TO RELEARN HOW TO HOLD POLES
CHAE-MIN INJURED HIS WRIST
CAR, THE GARDEN
GOSH… GET WELL SOON!
DOWOON
OH, DEAR
CHAE-MIN
HANG IN THERE, EVERYONE!
TARZZAN
I'M BRINGING VERY SWEET HIKING SNACKS
FROM THE US
CAR, THE GARDEN
SEE YOU SOON
DOWOON
YEAH, GET WELL SOON
CHAE-MIN
I'LL DO MY BEST!
A FEW DAYS LATER
THE DAY THEY GO TO JEJU ISLAND
GANGNAM, SEOUL
Hello.
DOWOON ARRIVES
-How have you been?
-Good.
You seem to be in good condition.
Now? Gosh.
THOUGHTS OF HIKING MAKE HIM SIGH
-We're not hiking yet.
-Of course not. That's good.
Am I the first to arrive?
You're here early.
THEY'LL ALL TAKE A BUS
TO GIMPO INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT
-President Tar.
-Hello.
-Hello, sir.
Hello.
I can tell you came from the US.
-Sorry?
-I can tell you're from the US.
TARZZAN WENT TO THE STATES RECENTLY
Tarzzan.
Hi.
Hello, Dowoon.
You're on TV so often these days.
Me? What do you mean?
My mother saw you on the show.
The one where you live alone.
Right.
DOWOON HIKED CHEONGGYESAN
ON ANOTHER SHOW TO SEE THE SUNRISE
I hiked Cheonggyesan in -10°C weather.
How was it?
After hiking with us,
did you develop any tricks?
Definitely. Cheonggyesan was so easy.
-Really?
-I took one hour to go up.
But Seoraksan was… Damn.
No, I just slept for five hours.
-You slept?
-Yes.
CHAE-MIN ARRIVES
-Hello.
-Hi.
Hello there.
A DEEP SIGH
Are the four of us going to sit here?
When Car-the comes,
it's going to be packed.
It'll be tight.
It'll look cute.
CAR-THE ARRIVES
I feel a bit…
Hold on.
I thought I'd feel better once I arrived.
Hello.
Hello, Jung-won.
Hi.
I made the stars wait.
Don't say that.
I haven't been
on this type of bus in ages.
ALL MEMBERS OF DESCEND CLUB ARE ABOARD
TO GIMPO INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT
Jeju Island has good food.
I'm looking forward to that.
I went straight to the hospital
the day I came back.
CAR, THE GARDEN WENT
TO THE HOSPITAL DUE TO INJURY
I prayed my knees gave out.
I wished my knees were totally injured.
I was ready to quit the show.
Please be injured badly.
But I went and took an X-ray,
and they said I was fine.
So I said, "Please check again."
I'm serious.
"Doctor, please."
"Then, take an MRI."
I couldn't take it there,
so I went to another hospital.
I took an MRI.
Nothing was wrong.
Really?
But I heard you had a ligament issue.
I think the doctor did their best
to find a problem.
I'm sure you have it too.
I'm sure you have the same issue.
-Chae-min too.
-Chae-min's wrist.
I heard Chae-min fell?
WEARING A WRIST BRACE DUE TO INJURY
It's okay.
It's just inflammation and whatnot.
If it hurts tomorrow,
I'm afraid I won't be able to climb.
Does it hurt now?
-Yes, it still hurts.
-What?
-I still have the brace on.
-So you can't go.
You can't hold the poles, right?
I don't think I can.
I was so depressed last night.
Why? You're on top
of the Melon music chart.
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN 14 YEARS,
HE'S NUMBER ONE ON MELON TOO
You shouldn't be feeling down.
Saying this while I'm sitting
in between these two
is a bit embarrassing,
but let me stay there for a while.
Just for a bit.
I know that as soon as you release
your albums,
things will change.
But let me stay there for a moment.
How's the air up there?
I didn't know before either.
At the top…
You knew, right?
You two knew about this feeling, right?
During my music career,
I didn't know
this kind of level in the air existed.
THE TOP TASTES SWEET
You're still number one.
It felt really good.
It's like the Huiungak Shelter.
Geez, stop it.
No joke. I literally got goosebumps.
Huiungak…
I erased its existence from my head.
How have you all been?
It's been over ten days
since the last shoot.
Other commitments felt much easier.
Chae-min was abroad too.
HE WENT TO A PARIS FASHION SHOW
Chae-min was at the fashion show.
A different world.
You're so cool, Chae-min.
Not at all.
Then, did you walk on a runaway?
Runaway?
Runway, not runaway.
BECOMES A RUNAWAY FROM THE FASHION SHOW
He shouldn't run away.
What was it?
Runaway and runway are the same.
Hold on, what was it called?
-Runway.
-Oh, runway.
-Runaway!
Runaway or runway. Same difference.
-They're all the same.
-As long as they get it.
Also, the person who used to work
at your agency
moved to my agency.
-There's one person who joined.
-Okay.
Do you go around saying this is fun?
Who on earth… What's their name?
You're going to get it.
Anyway, you came back from hiking
and told people at THEBLACKLABEL,
"It was fun."
You said that.
"What?"
"What's wrong with him?"
"Why would he go around saying that?"
Because of that,
I was a bit upset with you.
Hear me out.
After it was over, I got in the car
and barely spoke a word with my manager.
-What did you say?
-"Thank you."
"Thank you for coming all the way here."
I was so exhausted.
I didn't even say
anything like, "It was fun."
-It was distorted.
-Yes, it was.
-So that's what happened.
-Yes.
Let us all watch out.
Okay.
Don't say stuff like, "It was fun,"
"I enjoyed it,"
or "It was rewarding."
You don't have to worry about me.
I keep telling those around me
that I've been scammed.
I've said that a lot too.
Dowoon, in the group chat…
-Yes?
-Why do you type in a dialect?
I've seen people speak in a dialect,
but I've never seen anyone
text in a dialect too.
But Busan people do that often.
They type, "Go ahead" in a dialect.
DOWOON
YEAH, GET WELL SOON
HOW ARE YOUR LEGS?
ENJOY THE FOOD
CAN YOU OPEN THE DOOR?
I HEAR THEY SELL RAMYEON ON THE SUMMIT
A COLLECTION OF TEXTS
FROM A GYEONGSANG PERSON
"Jeju Island 'naena,'
I hear they sell ramyeon on the summit."
What's "naena"?
Jeju Island naena…
How do I explain this?
How do I explain "naena"?
-You wrote it.
-Jeju Island naena?
Naena.
There must be a meaning to it.
Naena Jeju Island…
"Well, on Jeju Island,
I heard they sell ramyeon on the summit."
It's "well." Like, "Well, on Jeju Island…"
Give us another example
of how you use naena.
An example.
The everyday usage.
When do you use it?
Naena, I can just use it like this.
What?
DID ANYONE UNDERSTAND THAT?
I don't think people use it often.
Not often? That's not true.
Is it language only you use?
No, a lot of people use naena.
Chae-min, that was great timing.
"What?"
NOBODY UNDERSTOOD NAENA
That was so good.
It means "likewise."
NAENA
A DIALECT WORD FOR "LIKEWISE" OR "ANYWAY"
-It's something like that.
-"Anyway."
Right. Wait, "anyway"?
Where are you from?
My accent's a mix of Changwon and Busan.
This is what it is.
Naena is like, "They're all the same."
-"They're all the same."
-Yes.
-"Likewise."
-Naena no difference.
-"Either way."
-Yes, something like that.
"Naena no difference."
I'm sorry, but in "Naena no difference,"
which part of that is Korean?
The "ji" part.
The "ji" at the end was Korean.
Something "ji."
"Ddoiddoi" isn't Korean?
I don't know.
Is it a slang?
"Slang"!
THE LINGUIST WHO GOES BEYOND BORDERS
It's slang?
Let's give a few dialect questions.
Okay.
DIALECT QUIZ STARTS
We're slowly getting quizzes now.
Here come the quizzes.
ANYTHING BUT HIKING WELCOMED
It's better to have them.
But I don't know
the correct intonation either.
She is from Gyeongsang Province.
Where are you from, U-jeong?
-Jinju.
Jinju?
Jinju is a bit on the outskirts.
Hey, are you nitpicking?
Jinju has 400,000 citizens!
I'm sorry.
People from Jinju will turn on you.
JINJU PEOPLE, COVER YOUR EARS
The western part of South Gyeongsang…
Jinju, "The City of Education."
Okay. I wonder if Dowoon knows this.
GYEONGSANG DIALECT QUIZ
I'll say them without the intonation.
You're so "kkaelbatda."
-Sorry?
See? Jinju is a bit on the outskirts.
"You're so foolish."
-Wrong.
Kkaelbatda.
I like everything about Chae-min,
but he's kkaelbatda.
"Dumb."
INSULTING HIMSELF
-He called himself that.
-He dissed himself.
He dissed himself.
Out of the four here,
Car, the garden is the most kkaelbatda.
-"Talkative."
-"Talkative"?
"Grumpy."
"Ugly"?
Seriously…
-Kkaelbatda?
WHAT'S "KKAELBATDA"?
"Make you angry"?
It's kkaelbatda.
The tone sounds like he's cursing.
Exactly. It doesn't sound nice.
"Why is he so kkaelbatda?"
Have you heard of it before?
-I've heard of "kkolbatda."
-I've heard of that too.
Who is the most kkaelbatda here?
I really think it's Car, the garden.
DOWOON AND TARZZAN DON'T KNOW EITHER
"Grumpy"?
Now that he actually gave us a quiz,
we can't answer.
It's difficult.
"Why is it so kkaelbatda?"
-It means "lazy."
-Really?
But for a word meaning "lazy,"
it sounds very antagonistic.
THEY'RE SO BAD,
SO DIFFICULTY IS LOWERED
It's clearly antagonistic.
Then, how about this?
"Neoljjatda."
I've heard of neoljjatda before.
THEY KNOW THE WORD
I know this one.
Dowoon, give us the native pronunciation.
Those from Seoul can guess.
I know this one,
but I've never used it before.
WHAT?
So you don't know how to say it?
I don't remember the meaning,
but I've heard it a lot before.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
What's with you?
Hey!
He's a fake. A fake Gyeongsang person.
He's a fake!
He was going for the down-to-earth vibe.
He was using a fake dialect.
-"Down-to-earth vibe"!
-"Fake dialect"!
"Going for the down-to-earth vibe"!
We need an example sentence.
Exactly.
Can you give us
an example sentence using neoljjatda?
"Neoljja me here."
"Leave me alone."
Wrong.
-"Drop me off here."
-Right.
Correct.
He's right.
CHAE-MIN IS CORRECT
Drop someone off.
They say neoljja. That's weird.
Normally, they say "drop off."
"Drop off" or "give a lift."
I'm disappointed, Dowoon.
You were a fake.
He could actually be a true Seoulite.
Totally.
If that's the case, he's incredible.
We got here quick.
SOON ARRIVING
AT GIMPO INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT
Actually, the real hike
will start tomorrow.
Today, as hiking club members,
you'll prepare for it
and build up your teamwork.
HALLASAN HIKE IS TOMORROW
Today is for you to get ready.
You'll be taking it easy today.
Right, President Tar?
President Tar,
could you brief us on the schedule?
I need to see the schedule.
I don't remember.
3 DAYS AGO
Hello.
You planned a lot when you were in LA.
A LONG TEXT MESSAGE FROM LA
3 DAYS AND 2 NIGHTS IN JEJU
What was the criteria for the plan?
Well, the criteria was,
"How can we make use
of the little time we have on Jeju Island
to go and do some fun things?"
Okay, then.
PRESIDENT TAR
AMBITIOUSLY PREPARED THEIR JEJU TRIP
Yes, we'll depart,
and arrive at Jeju Airport
between 11:00 a.m. and 1:00 p.m.
PICK UP RENTAL CAR
AT 1:00 P.M. AT AIRPORT
We'll rent a car.
-Then, we'll go for lunch.
-Nice.
Lunch is cold raw abalone soup.
-Sounds good.
What do we do next?
And for a physical activity,
we'll go to Jeju Big Ball Land.
-Big Ball Land.
At least we get to ride a plane.
STARTING UNDER PRESIDENT TAR'S DIRECTION
DESCEND CLUB'S FIRST EXPEDITION
TO JEJU ISLAND
Where's the mountain?
DESCEND CLUB IS HAPPY
IF THERE'S NO HIKING
Look how close we've become.
Tarzzan found this place?
Good job finding it.
THEY'LL HAVE A LUXURIOUS TRIP
THANKS TO THEIR FOODIE PRESIDENT
This is so good.
Good job finding it.
THUMBS UP
I want to feed the sheep too.
He's actually doing it.
THE PRESIDENT UNLEASHES HIS PLAYFUL SIDE
THE OTHERS BECOME WEIRDER
Hey, what's going on?
You little punk.
Whoa!
Subtitle translation by: Kim Yeeun